{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"EXTRACTS a section of a string and returns it as a new string.","correct_answer":".shift","incorrect_answers":[".pop",".slice"," "]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"JavaScript's way of making lists.","correct_answer":"Index","incorrect_answers":["Array","Element"," "]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Arrays inside other arrays.","correct_answer":"Index","incorrect_answers":["Nested Array","Element"," "]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Contents of a const array can be changed, but cannot be reassigned a new array or a different value.","correct_answer":"Mutable","incorrect_answers":["Array Literal","Element"," "]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Removes the FIRST element from an array and returns it.","correct_answer":".pop","incorrect_answers":[".slice",".shift"," "]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Each content item inside an array.","correct_answer":"Array Literal","incorrect_answers":["Element","Array"," "]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Each element in an array has a numbered position known as...","correct_answer":"Index","incorrect_answers":["Nested Arrays","Array"," "]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"REMOVES the last item of an array.","correct_answer":".push","incorrect_answers":[".slice",".pop"," "]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"ADDS one or more element to the BEGINNING of an array and returns the new length.","correct_answer":".shift","incorrect_answers":[".unshift",".pop"," "]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Creates an array by wrapping items in square brackets.","correct_answer":"Array","incorrect_answers":["Array Literal","Nested Arrays"," "]}]}
